drinktrade.com 2019-05-30

# Trade Privacy Policy: Detailed Privacy Information | Trade Coffee

**TRADE PRIVACY POLICY**

 _Effective Date: April 5, 2018_

This Privacy Policy of Seed Leaf LLC d/b/a Trade (“ **Trade** ”) applies to information Trade obtains from its websites, including the Trade Coffee Co site and its services (collectively, the “ **Service** ”), and information you may provide to us via other means of communication.

We respect your privacy and will strive to protect your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes how Trade collects, uses, shares and secures the information you provide. It also describes choices you may make regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. Please note that this Privacy Policy is incorporated within our Terms of Service for Trade and, unless we otherwise define a term in this Privacy Policy, a capitalized term used in this Privacy Policy has the meaning defined in the Terms.

You agree that by using the Service you acknowledge that you have read and consent to the collection, use and sharing of your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, do not use the Service. This Privacy Policy does not apply to websites not operated by Trade, including any to which the Service provides a link or which link to the Service.

 **MODIFICATION OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time, as new features, technology, or legal requirements arise. You may always determine if this Privacy Policy has changed by checking the Effective Date at the top of this page. If we make a significant change, we’ll notify you and, where required, seek your consent. If we update this Privacy Policy, you are free to decide whether to accept the updated terms or to stop using the Service; your continued use of the Service after the effectiveness of that update will be deemed to represent your consent to the provisions in the updated Privacy Policy.

 **INFORMATION COLLECTED**

 _Customer Provided Information_

We may collect and store any personal information you provide on our site or in some other manner. When we refer to "personal information" in this Privacy Policy, we mean information that can be associated with a specific person and could be used to identify that specific person whether from that data alone or from that data in combination with other information that we have access to. We do not consider personal information to include information that has been made anonymous or aggregated so that it can no longer be used, whether in combination with other information or otherwise, to identify a specific person. Personal information includes Customer Information, such as your name, address, email address, telephone number, billing and shipping addresses and financial information such as your payment method (valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information). In addition, if you choose to use certain features of the Service, we may require you to provide additional personal information such as shopping preferences and demographics.

We may also collect and store personal information that you provide to us about other people. If you use our Service to send others (friends, relatives, colleagues, etc.) a Gift Card, a product, information that may interest them or messages (such as invitations) through our system, we may store your personal information and the personal information of each such recipient.

 _Automatically Collected Information_

We automatically collect information from your browser when you visit our site. This information includes your IP address, your browser type and language, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us and the referring website address.

When you visit our site, we may assign your computer one or more cookies to facilitate access to our site and to personalize your online experience. Through the use of a cookie, we may automatically collect information about your online activity on our site, such as the web pages you visit, the links you click and the searches you conduct on our site.

We may use standard Internet technology, such as web beacons, tracking pixels and other similar technologies, to track your use of our site. We also may include web beacons in email messages or newsletters to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

We may use third-party advertising companies to help tailor content or to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and web beacons to measure advertising effectiveness (such as which web pages are visited or what products are purchased and in what amount). Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and web beacons is not linked to any personal information collected by us.

 _Information from Other Sources_

We may also periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from our business partners, contractors and other third parties, and we may add such information to our account information or other information we have collected. In addition, if you access the Service using log-in credentials from another website or service (for example, Google or Facebook), we may obtain both personal and non-personal information from such other website or service, which you may review and adjust within such other services.

 **INFORMATION USE AND DISCLOSURE**

We use information that we collect about you for our internal purposes, including:

· to establish your Customer account with our Service, and to communicate with you about our Service, including products or services that may be of interest to you;

· to support and enhance your use of the Service and provide you with customer support;

· to process your order payments, and deliver the products and services that you have requested;

· to conduct research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content;

· to serve you content and advertising tailored to your interests on our site;

· to enforce our terms and conditions and otherwise manage our business; and

· to perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

We may share your personal information with our authorized Service Providers to provide a number of services related to the operation of our Service, including fulfilling orders, processing payments, delivering packages, providing customer service and marketing assistance, performing business and sales analysis, supporting our website functionality and supporting features offered through our site. In addition, we may share information that you provide to us as well as information that we collect from third parties to serve you ads tailored to your interests on our site and on other websites or third party services.

From time to time, we may share your personally identifiable information with our strategic and business partners, including our bank, insurance and audit firms, as well as marketing and business development partners. We may share personally identifiable or other information with our affiliates and business partners and across our websites, applications, social media pages and other online platforms. We may transfer personally identifiable information as an asset in connection with a proposed or actual merger or sale (including any transfers made as part of an insolvency or bankruptcy proceeding) involving all or part of our business or as part of a corporate reorganization, stock sale or other change in control.

We may disclose such information in response to requests from law enforcement officials conducting investigations, subpoenas or court orders, or if we believe we are otherwise required to disclose such information by law. We also may release personal information where we believe disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights, enforce our Terms or other agreements or to protect ourselves or others.

Any third party to whom we may disclose personal information may have their own privacy policy which describes how they use and disclose personal information. Those policies will govern such third party’s use, handling and disclosure of your personal information unless we have entered into a contract with other terms or conditions. These entities or their servers may be located either inside or outside the United States.

We may use aggregated non-personal information for internal business purposes, such as improving our site. In addition, we may share aggregated non-personal information (such as the number of daily visitors to our site) with any of the above parties. We may also share aggregated information that contains no personally identifiable information with any other third party for any other purpose, including for marketing purposes and for conducting general business analysis.

While we use contractual and other measures to ensure protection of personal information, the laws and regulations relating to privacy and personal information protection in other jurisdictions may not be the same as, or similar to, your local privacy laws. The governments, courts, law enforcement or regulatory agencies in these other jurisdictions may be able to request disclosure of personal information through the laws of these countries.

Some third parties’ embedded content or plugins on the Service, such as Facebook “Like” buttons, may allow their operators to learn that you have visited our website, and they may combine this information with other, identifiable information they have collected about your visits to other websites or online services.

 **DATA SECURITY**

We are committed to protecting the security of your information and take reasonable precautions to protect it. We use industry standard encryption to protect your data in transit and while it is stored on our servers. This is commonly referred to as transport layer security (TLS) or secure socket layer (SSL) technology. However, internet data transmissions cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure the security of information during its transmission between you and us. Accordingly, you acknowledge that when you transport such information, you do so at your own risk.

Some of the important safeguards we deploy are digital encryption, digital and physical access controls deployed and managed by our third-party data centers and administrators, and information access authorization controls. Again, data centers and our third-party service providers are not guaranteed to be 100% secure, and so you acknowledge that your information stored in such data centers or service providers is at your own risk.

If we learn of a system breach, we may attempt to notify you and provide information on protective steps, if available, using the Customer Information that you have provided to us or by posting a notice on our web site and/or via our Service and other communication platforms. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive such notices in writing.

 **RETAINING INFORMATION**

We retain Customer Information, certain communications with you, and analytics generated by the operation of our Service (collectively, the “ **Service Output** ”), as long as we believe it is necessary and relevant for the operation of our Service. Our Service operates on computers owned and/or operated by Trade and located in third-party data centers in the United States and, possibly in other countries in the future.

Under certain circumstances we may retain Customer Information after the termination of a Customer account. We do this to ensure that the Service is not interrupted and none of the Service Output is lost due to interrupted Service subscriptions or other unanticipated events. We may also retain Customer Information after a Customer account is terminated to prevent fraud, collect any payments owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigation, enforce our Terms, comply with applicable legal data retention obligations and take other actions permitted by law.

 **UPDATING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES**

 _Account Information_

If you have an account with our Service, you have the ability to review and update your personal information online by logging into your account. You can also review and update your personal information by contacting us at SUPPORT@TRADECOFFEECO.COM.

 _Marketing Communications ___

You may choose not to receive marketing email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in any marketing email. You may choose to opt out of receiving marketing communications by Texts in the manner described in ourTerms of Service. It may take up to three (3) business days for us to process an opt-out request. However, please note that we may send you what we consider to be important Service-related messages, customer service responses or other communications relating to inappropriate use of the Service or requests from third-parties to access information in your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

 _Location Data_

You can choose not to share your location data by adjusting the applicable settings on your mobile device (the manufacturer or your service provider should be able to provide assistance).

 _Cookies and Other Technologies_

As noted above, we use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies for purposes such as improving your experience using our Service. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, please note that you may not be able to sign in or use some of the features offered on our site and your experience with the Service may be degraded. Please also note that if you have multiple computers or change computers, or use multiple browsers, you will need to disable cookies for each such computer or browser.

 _Limiting Sharing_

We will use reasonable efforts to honor any request that we not share your personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes. You may make such a request by updating your information at [**WWW.TRADECOFFEECO.COM**](https://www.tradecoffeeco.com/)or by sending a written request to the address below:

By mail:

Trade Coffee Co

401 Park Drive, 9th Floor

Boston, MA 02215

Attn: Privacy Concerns

YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to SUPPORT@TRADECOFFEECO.COM or write to us at:

Trade Coffee Co

401 Park Drive, 9th Floor

Boston, MA 02215

Attn: Privacy Concerns

We will honor any statutory right you might have to access, modify or erase your personal information. Where you have a legal right to request access or request the modification or erasure of information, we can still withhold that access or decline to correct information in some cases in accordance with applicable law, but will give you reasons if we do so.

CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under age 13. If you are not 18 or older, you are not authorized to use the Service. Parents should be aware that there are parental control tools available online that you can use to prevent your children from submitting information online without parental permission or from accessing material that is harmful to minors.

ACCESS TO THE SERVICES FROM OUTSIDE OF THE UNITED STATES

If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that Trade is the data controller for the Service, and we may store and process your personal information on computers in the US and elsewhere in the world where our data centers are located. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. By using the Service, you consent to your information being collected, used and disclosed as described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:

By mail:

Trade Coffee Co

401 Park Drive, 9th Floor

Boston, MA 02215

Attn: Privacy Concerns

By email: **SUPPORT@TRADECOFFEECO.COM**
